[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Adventures in Babysitting Chris is accused of being a centerfold from what mens magazine?", "correct_answer": "Playboy", "incorrect_answers": ["Hustler", "Maxim", "Penthouse"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these terms refer to the chambers of the heart -- the two on top and the two on the bottom respectively?", "correct_answer": "Atria and Ventricles", "incorrect_answers": ["Pericardia and Myocardia", "Ventricles and Atria", "Atria and Ventricle, Atria and Ventricle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this cult film directed by John Carpenter both Clint Eastwood and Jack Nicholson were considered for the lead role.", "correct_answer": "Big Trouble in Little China", "incorrect_answers": ["Raiders of the Lost Ark", "Iron Eagle", "The Fly"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It only takes one witness to spoil the perfect crime is the tag line from which movie?", "correct_answer": "Rear Window", "incorrect_answers": ["North By North West", "Vertigo", "The Man Who Knew Too Much"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Stegosaurus had back legs that were twice as long as its front legs.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which movie featured the line I had a partner, I would have taken a bullet for him. You Im having a hard time not shooting?", "correct_answer": "National Security", "incorrect_answers": ["Bad Boys II", "Bad Boys", "Bluestreak"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the first name of the actress who married David Duchovny in 1997?", "correct_answer": "Tea", "incorrect_answers": ["Lea", "Bea", "Mia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Back to the Future, Marty told Lorraines mother that he was in this branch of the military.", "correct_answer": "Coast Guard", "incorrect_answers": ["Army", "Navy", "Marines"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Forrest Gump, this actor played Lt. Dan Taylor, the commanding officer of Forrest when he first arrived in Vietnam.", "correct_answer": "Gary Sinise", "incorrect_answers": ["Jack Nicholson", "Ed Harris", "Robert Duvall"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1973 movie is this quote from: Youre telling me that I should take my daughter to a witch doctor? Is that it??", "correct_answer": "The Exorcist", "incorrect_answers": ["Alice, Sweet Alice", "The Sentinel", "The Wicker Man"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which U.S. state has been nicknamed The Silver State?", "correct_answer": "Nevada", "incorrect_answers": ["Nebraska", "North Dakota", "New Mexico"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When you add the previously prepared seasoning, pour one third of a cup of this beverage and wait for it to evaporate.", "correct_answer": "Wine", "incorrect_answers": ["Rum", "Beer", "Martini"]}]